Yahoo, yahoo, what are you doing?
やっほー やっほー 何してるの?
What, what are you doing?
え、何してる?
I'm standing.
立ってます
Chin Chin?
チンチンが?
No.
違います
What about that?
それのチンチンの話?
Maybe so.
そうかもしれないです
How are you doing lately?
どうですか最近?
I'm enjoying it.
楽しんでます
Are you having fun?
楽しんでる?
Where did you go?
どっか行った?
I'm going.
行きます
Where did you go?
どこ行ったの?
Atami.
あたみ
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
hot spring?
温泉?
I'm going to a hot spring.
温泉行ってます
It's really good.
めっちゃいいじゃん
Why didn't you invite me?
なんで誘って来いなかった?
Did you want to go?
行きたかったですか?
Then I'll definitely go.
じゃあぜひ行きます
copper?
どう?
Are you feeling kind of horny?
なんか ムラムラしてる?
Are you horny?
ムラムラしてます?
copper?
どう?
Are you doing it?
してる?
I am doing.
してます
I think they need some stimulation.
刺激が欲しいんじゃないかなと
yes?
そう?
want?
欲しい?
want.
欲 しい
It's not exciting, right?
刺激ないでしょ?
It's definitely not exciting.
確かに刺激ないですね
Well, I guess you could call it a surprise.
ちょっとじゃあさ、 サプライズっていうか
Surprise?
サプライズ?
Because I have a surprise.
サプライズあるから
Come on.
おい で
Surprise?
サプライズ?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Acchan!
あっちゃん!
It's Acchan!
あっちゃんだ!
Super cute!
超かわいい!
Acchan?
あっちゃん?
It's Acchan!
あっちゃんだ!
Awesome!
すげー!
gratitude!
感激!
Can I come in for a moment?
ちょっと入っていい?
It's Acchan, right?
あっちゃんだよね?
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
Don't you hate it?
嫌じゃない?
Highest!
最高!
That's great.
最高だね
It's the best.
最高です
You're in trouble.
困ってるじゃん
It looks like it's going to melt.
とろけちゃいそう
I was surprised.
びっくりした
I won't try hard.
頑張んない
It's the best.
最高だよ
Super happy.
超幸せ
Super happy?
超幸せ?
It's black.
黒なんだね
Looks like an adult.
大人っぽいね
Acchan.
あっちゃん
It came out.
出てきた
You're laughing when your lips are licked.
口首舐められて笑ってるじゃなーい
fun?
楽しい?
fun.
楽しい
Will I be able to get rid of it if I do my best?
口首思いっきりしたら取れちゃうかな?
I think I can get it.
取れそう
Can I take it?
取っていい?
Scar
ス カ
It's long.
ート 長いね
長いね
I want it a little bit.
ちょっと欲しい欲しい
want?
欲しい?
What do you want?
欲 しい 何?
I'm playing.
遊んでるよ
Butts are meant to be played with, right?
お尻だって遊ぶためのもんでしょ?
Puni Puni.
ぷにぷに
Highest.
最高
It's the best.
最高です
This this.
これこれ
This is what I was looking for.
これだよ、求めてたものは
Open your legs.
足開いて
Good.
よいしょ
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
Take your feet.
足をさ
Please hang it on the wall.
壁にかけてください
Raise your legs.
足あげて
oh yeah.
そうそう
It's slimy.
ヌルヌルだよ
Were you excited?
興奮してたのかな?
Isn't it?
ないでしょ?
Because it's long.
長いからさ
Can I take it?
取っていい?
Her butt is also cute.
お尻もかわいい
So slimy.
すごいヌルヌル
oh.
おお
Awesome.
すげー
A mess.
ぐちゃぐちゃ
That's amazing.
すっごいね
On my stomach.
お腹いで
That's honest.
素直だね
Get it down.
下出して
Eat this.
これ食べて
Eat, Acchan.
食べて、あっちゃん
It feels so good.
すっげー気持ちいい
You know what to do.
どうするか分かるよね
I know what to do.
どうするか分かる
I took it there.
取っちゃったよ、そこって
what happened?
どうしたの?
Why did you laugh?
なんで笑ったの?
I'm the type of person who laughs when I feel sick.
気持ち悪くなると笑っちゃうタイプだ
It felt so good, Acchan.
めっちゃ気持ちよかったよ、あっちゃん
Was it exciting?
刺激的だった?
Yeah.
うん
It's still not enough, right?
ちょっとまだ足りないでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
how was it?
どうだった?
I was surprised.
びっくりした
That's too funny.
笑えすぎるやつ
It seems like it's not enough.
ちょっと足りないそうだね
A fan?
ファンが?
fan?
ファン?
I'm a fan.
ファンなんです
Acchan.
あっちゃん
Ah-chan.
あっ ちゃん
I have some really good news.
めっちゃいいニュースが
It's out.
出てる
It's coming out, somehow.
出ちゃってるよ、なんか
Usually?
普段から?
Is this the style?
こういうスタイル?
That kind of style?
そういうスタイル?
Is this style also like this?
こっちもこういうスタイル?
amazing.
すごい
He wants to come out.
出たがりだ
It's not settled.
収まってないもんね
I can take this too.
こっちも撮れてる
Are you wearing sexy underwear?
エロい下着付けてるのか
Erotic underwear.
エロい下着
Are you wearing erotic underwear?
エ ロい下着付けてるのか
I feel like black is very seductive.
黒って、すごい誘惑するって感じするよね
surely.
確かに
Really.
本当に
It's true.
本当 だ
Why isn't this string bread included?
なんでこの紐パンなんか入ってないの?
Isn't it erotic?
エロくない?
This string bread.
ちょっとこの紐パン
That's dangerous.
やばいよね
She had such an erotic body.
こんなエロい体してたんだったじゃん
I wanted you to be happy, so I brought you something like this.
喜んでもらいたくてさ、 こういうの持ってきたんだ
Do you understand?
わかる?
this.
これ
I want you to be happy.
喜んでほしくてさ
You need a microphone, after all.
マイク必要だよね、やっぱりね
Oh yeah.
ああ、そうそう
That microphone was shining.
そのマイク光ってた
It shone.
光った
This mic also has a lot of remixes.
このマイクもちょっとね、いろいろ リミックがあってさ
That's how you say a present.
プレゼントをこう言うってことだよね
Oh, I saw it, I saw it.
あ、見えた見えた
It's this way, it's this way.
こっちだよ、こっちだよ
What are your thoughts on the movie?
映画の心境は?
Ah, I don't know anymore.
あ、もう分かんない
Don't you understand?
分かんないの?
It's cute.
可愛いね
Don't you understand?
分かんないのか
I don't know.
分かんない
Let me help you understand a lot of things.
いろいろ分かってもらおうね
Please understand
分 かってもらお
cormorant.
う
If you don't understand, your nipples are so big, aren't you?
分 かんないというわけには、 乳首ビビビンなんだね、
This is it.
これね
You know the nipples, I'm sure.
乳首は分かってるんだね、きっとね
I know the nipples.
乳首は分かってる
That's amazing.
それすごいね
It's funny how you pinch it like that.
面白い、そうやって挟むの
like this?
こう?
Does it feel good to clink like this?
こうやってクリクリするの、気持ちいいのかな、
this.
これ
This is getting more and more solid.
どんどん固まってるね、これ
Both are stuck.
両方挟まれちゃってる
You can fit this in.
これ、挟めるね
I'm sure there are many others.
他にもいっぱいあると思うんだけど
This is really catchy.
すごい挟めてるね、これ
You're doing it again.
またネッパしてるね
Hey.
ねえ
Chestnuts are binging, but this is a little.
栗、ビンビンなんだけど、これちょっと
amazing.
すごい
Chestnut, that's a bit scary.
栗、やばいね、ちょっとね
It's wet.
濡れてるしね
Has it been like this since I arrived?
来たときからこんなのあったのかな、
surely.
きっと
Yeah.
うん
They did it a while ago, but I wasn't there.
なんかさっきやったんですね、俺いなかったけど
There was a surprise.
サプライズあった
It's a surprise present.
サプライズプレゼントだね
Yeah.
うん
This chestnut is Pocky long.
栗がポッキー長いね、これ
That's cool.
かっこいいね
It stands up well.
立ちいいね
It stands up well, really.
立ちいいね、ほんとに
Can hold both.
両方挟める
amazing.
すごい
But is it stuck?
でも挟まってる?
This is what's stuck.
挟まってる、これ
Isn't that the feeling?
その感覚じゃない?
This is a bit.
これがちょっと
It will shine even more.
さらに光らしちゃう
It's chestnut glowing though.
栗光ってるけどね
Chestnut: It's glowing, just a little.
栗 光ってる、ちょっとね
It's shining.
光ってるねー
In this way, we can actually make this place shine,
こうやってさ、実際、 ここも光らせるの、
Until inside.
中まで
Is that so?
そういうこと?
So that you can see it.
見えるように
Idols shine on the inside too, don't they?
アイドルって中も光るんじゃないですか
That's it.
そういうことだ
I feel like I'm pulling the strings.
糸引いてる、なんか
Yeah.
うん
難
Yes.
しい
Is it difficult?
難 しいの?
Seriously?
マジで?
It takes a little longer to apply with a thin pin.
少し細いピンピンで塗るのが ちょっと長いね
Like a quality idol.
素質アイドルみたいに
Yeah.
うん
It's really beautiful.
ほんと綺麗だし
Yeah.
うん
This is beautiful.
綺麗だね、これは
Take a look from here.
ちょっとこっちから見て
It's coming out really nicely.
すっごい綺麗に込み出してる
I went in.
入っちゃった
There's a lot in it.
めっちゃ入ってる
Look, look.
ほ ら、ほら
There's so much in it.
こんなにっぷり入ってる
There's so much in it, I guess.
すっごいすっごい入ってるね、なんかね
I can feel it soaking in my hands.
手にしぐり浸れちゃってるね、なんかね
My hips are shaking though.
腰震えてるけど
Yeah.
うん
Did it hurt?
痛った?
Did it feel that good?
そんな気持ちよかったか
Did you wear underwear?
下着着たの?
Yes, I wore it.
はい、着ました
Was it cold?
寒かった?
Shall I make you warm?
温かくしてあげようか
Will it keep you warm?
温かくしてくれるんですか?
I'll keep you warm.
温かくしてあげまーす
warm?
温かい?
warm.
温かい
Human futon.
人間布団
warm.
温かい
I'll make it red
赤くしてあげるから
hey.
ね
cold?
寒 い?
so?
そんなに?
Another person is a meat futon.
もう一人、肉布団
Meat futon?
肉布団?
The meat futon is coming, then.
肉布団が来るよ、じゃあ
The meat futon is cold.
肉布団、寒いって
It's cold.
寒 いって
Hands, hands.
手が、手が
lie?
嘘?
hot.
暑い
Damn, that's cold.
くそ冷たいね
My feet are cold too.
足も冷たいね
cold.
冷たい
It's cold, my feet.
冷たいね、足
It's really cold.
本当 に冷たいね
That's surprising.
びっくりだね
warm?
温かい?
Uncle, just a little bit.
おじさんね、ちょっとね
It's warm on the way home.
お帰りの上に温かいの
warm.
温かい
As expected, it was warm.
さ すがに、温かい
It's warm when it's soft.
サ サ ってると温かい
It's warm when it's dry.
ササってると温かいからね
Goosebumps...
鳥肌が...
I have goosebumps.
鳥肌がね
I'm getting goosebumps.
鳥肌さってるね
The old man doesn't like these goosebumps, so he's cleaning them off.
この鳥肌、おじさんが嫌だから、鳥肌掃ってるわけじゃないか
Because it's cold...
寒いから...
Just touch my uncle.
ちょっと、おじさんに触ってて
Uncle, it's warm.
おじさん、温かいから
Where is it cold?
どこが寒い?
number one?
一番?
all?
全部?
Is everything cold?
全部寒いのか
It's really cold.
本当に冷たいね
You have to touch it directly to warm it.
直接触って温めないといけない
My knees get cold.
膝は冷えるからね
it hurts?
痛い?
My knees get cold.
膝は冷えるからね
I need to warm it up a little.
ちょっと温めないといけないから
It's weak, isn't it?
弱いのよね
Are you weak?
弱いの?
Both inside and out.
裏も裏も
My knees need to cool down.
膝は冷めないといけない
You forget about being ticklish and cold, right?
くすぐったいと寒いの忘れるでしょ?
surely.
確かに
In the end, what matters is where you put your consciousness.
結局意識をどこに持っていくかが重要だから
It's important to distract yourself.
気をそらすの大事だよね
amazing.
すごい
Look, it's getting hot.
ほら、暑くなってきた
It's getting hot, isn't it?
暑くなってるでしょ?
hot.
暑い
That's right.
そうなんだよ
Shouldn't we exercise a lot?
いっぱい運動しようかじゃない?
Certainly, if you exercise a lot.
い っぱい運動すれば確かにね
It's going to be warm.
暖かくなるね
Let's get our butts filtered.
お尻をフィルチャーしよう
Let's filter your ass.
お 尻フィルチャーしよう
I like that.
それ好き
It's a healing gesture.
治す仕草がね
Let me fix it myself.
治してもらおうか自分で
Oh, is that what it feels like?
あ、そういう感じ?
Ah, nice.
あ、いいね
Butt up, I like that feeling.
お尻を上にね、あの感じ好き
When you pull it tightly towards the front.
前の方にキュッと引っ張ると
Ah, it's perfect.
あ、 ピッタリして
Good from an ass table theorist.
お尻表論家からいいね
It's good for being worn on the hands of writers.
表論家の手装着にいいね
That's why I'm looking at you.
それで見しかけてるから
A little small.
ちょっと小さい
It's perfect.
ピ ッタリして
Really nice style.
本当スタイルいい
I'm constricted.
くびれてるし
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
this.
これ
This is a good thing to have when you're having sex.
これ、セクスしてる時にここ持つといいやつだよね
Do you know?
知ってる?
Take it here.
ここ持ってさ
I get tired of having you carry me.
持ってくれて疲れちゃうんだよ
I can't help it, this.
しょうがないね、これ
I don't know because the pants are black.
パンツが黒いからわかんないけどね
Try opening it halfway.
ちょっと 半分開いてみてね
There was liquid even through my pants.
パンツ越しにだっても液体が
Isn't it easy to apply?
塗りやすいんじゃない?
Is it easy to apply?
塗りやすいの?
塗りやすい?
cute.
可愛い
The inner bass is solid.
インナーバッサルがしっかりしてる
Look, look at this.
見て見て、これ
What is this?
これ何?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Isn't this a little too wet?
これはちょっと濡れすぎじゃないかな?
This is so sensitive.
敏感なんだね、これ
Did you notice?
気づいたの?
Beautiful pie pie.
綺麗なパイパイ
I can't open it because it's slimy.
ぬるぬるしてるから開けない
Are you going to point it out?
指すべっちゃうの?
Are you getting melty?
トロトロしちゃうの?
It's not like I'm drinking and fooling around.
お酒してふざけてるわけじゃない
It's too clear.
くりがぼっきすぎてさ
The swelling is weak.
膨らみが弱いんですよ
The chestnut bulge is a bright light, isn't it?
くりぼっきし膨らみが丸明かりなんでしょ
It came out.
出てきた
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
cute.
可愛い
Embarrassing girls are cute.
恥ずかしい女の子って可愛いからね
It's important to be ashamed, really.
恥大って大事よ、本当に
Shame is important.
恥 大が大事
You look like my older sister.
お姉みたくなってるね
Press further.
さらに押して
This is with my own hands.
ここは自分の手で
Look ahead carefully.
前見てちゃんと
It's erotic that you're attracting people.
人引いてるもんだってエロいわ
If you're embarrassed, you'll just sit down and do it.
恥ずかしいと座ってやるんだね
My mouth doesn't seem to swell.
口ちょっと膨らまずみたいな
It's cute.
可愛いわ
What are you thinking?
何考えてるの?
It's growing.
伸びてるやつよ
The juice is growing.
汁伸びてる
Hot soup, because it's Acchan.
熱汁、あっちゃんだから
Wow, it's so warm.
すげえ、あったかい
Is it warm?
あったかい?
The juice will come out.
汁が出てきちゃうね
Because I can see inside the hole.
穴の中まで見てるから
there were
あ った
shellfish?
か い?
A situation where you are looking inside the hole of the pussy.
おまんこの穴の中を見てる状況
Have you ever been seen this deep?
こんな奥まで見られたことある?
Not though.
ないけどね
I have an erotic pussy.
エロいまんこしてる
You say it's cold, but it's really warm.
寒い寒いって言ってるけど、すごいあったかいよ
I feel like I'm floating.
ほっかよろみたい
I like the style of this line.
スタイルいいね、このライン
Upper body.
体を上半身
Ah, yes, this.
あ、そうそう、これ
This is an idol.
これがアイドルだ
The holes are clean too.
穴もきれいだ
I'll take a look at that hole too.
そっちの穴も見ちゃう
You can see all the way to this hole, just this.
こっちの穴まで丸見えだよ、ちょっとこれ
This is terrible.
やばいね、これね
One, two, three.
一本、二本、三本ってね
You don't know the number of Shiba.
知らないでしょ、しばの数
You can tell me.
教えてもらえるよ
Probably around 30 pieces.
30本くらいかな
Isn't there more?
もっとあるんじゃない?
I have a bit of a poor eye for details.
細かいのまで、ちょっと目が悪くて
The real tone is spot on.
本当のタチがきっちりだよ
When it comes to idols.
アイドルとなるとね
It's a body you worked hard to build.
努力して作り上げた体だよ
Really?
ほ んとかね
I have a feeling this is a butt.
お尻予感うしいわ、これ
The style is terrible.
ス タイルやばいな
Why does it have this style?
なんでこんなスタイルになっちゃう?
I'm talking about absolute temperature.
絶対温度とかしてるよ
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to create this style.
じゃなきゃ、このスタイル作り上げられない
what happened?
どうしたの?
It just smells a bit, but
ちょっと臭い感じだけなんだけど、
Sorry.
ごめんね
This smelled bad.
臭いダメだったわ、これ
It's good to be embarrassed, right?
恥ずかしいのがいいでしょ
A nice little fragrance.
いいフレグランスがちょっと
I'm seriously running away from this.
本気で逃げられてる、これ
He was serious about running away.
逃げ方が本気だったもんね
The amount of effort put into it was serious.
力の入り具合が本気だった
It's a mess.
ぐっちゃぐちゃじゃん
What is this?
これ何?
Serious soup?
本気汁?
This is some serious juice.
本気汁だね、ちょっとね、これは
This Sill is serious.
このシルは本気だわ
Put your feet up.
足を上げて
The pitch-black touch is erotic.
真っ黒な触り方、エロい
I feel a sense of positivity.
なんか、積極性を感じるよ
What's wrong with ego?
エゴにどんよく?
nice.
いいね
Shall we do it?
やっちゃう?
Attraction.
アトラクションをね
Sit down for a moment.
ちょっと座って
Being held behind the size.
サイズの後ろを持たれて
nice.
いいね
This kid is so light.
軽いね、この子ね
You can make ekiben or something like that.
駅弁とかできちゃうね
You can do it, this.
できちゃうね、これね
A lot of things came out.
なんかいっぱい出ちゃったよ
I was watching it.
見てたらさ
Seriously?
マジ?
I was able to hide my line of sight, my line of sight.
目線、目線、隠せちゃった
I'll hide my line of sight.
目線、これ隠れちゃう
That's amazing.
すごいね
He licked me.
舐めてくれた
We made first contact, right?
ファーストコンタクトできたでしょ?
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
Chin Chin is watching and laughing.
チンチンがみながら笑ってるよ
It's cute.
可愛いね
I'll lick your dick too.
チンチンも舐めてあげちゃう
Isn't it easy to lick?
舐めやすいでしょ?
It's just the right size, right?
ちょうど収まっちゃうサイズでしょ?
It's good to be proactive.
積極的でいいね
I was so happy, kid.
嬉しかったね、今の子
happy?
嬉しい?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's embarrassing to have two at the same time.
2本同時恥ずかしい
So one by one.
じゃあ1本ずつ
It was so slippery that I got into it, this is it.
ぬるぬるすぎて入っちゃったね、これね
Isn't it so disgusting?
めちゃくちゃしむくない?
It's hard to lick, so why not put up two?
舐めにくいから、2本立てる?
Good, good.
よ いしょ、よいしょ
Is it different from what you think?
気と違うかな?
TRUE?
本当?
This one is worse.
こっちの方がダメだね
Grab me by the neck.
首つかんでね
I can't walk like this.
このまま散歩できない
good
よ い
Sho.
しょ
It's a little too decided.
ちょっと、 決まりすぎちゃった
Robocar is being meddled with.
ロボーカー、口出しされちゃってるもん
hey.
ね
It's a cute pussy, really.
か わいいリマンコしてるね、ほんとね
Can I leave it out like this?
このまま出しちゃっていい?
I'll take it out.
出しちゃうよ
Get on your knees.
膝立ちになって
Strengthen your body and stomach.
体にお腹に力入れて
A lot was served.
いっぱい出されちゃったね
Did it feel that good?
そんな気持ちよかった?
Can I tell you?
お口出していい?
It felt a little too good, so I let out a lot.
ちょっと気持ちよすぎて、いっぱい出しちゃった
You got your body dirty.
体を汚しちゃったね
Go take a shower and clean your bed.
シャワー行って、きれいに敷きなよ